Guide to the Henry R. Luce Papers 1894-2004 (bulk, 1932-1967) MS 3014
New-York Historical Society
- Series V. Subject Name Files, 1894-1995 (bulk 1933-1967); 30.1 Linear feet
  - Subseries V.B. Name Files B, 1910-1974 (bulk 1933-1967)
    - Rankin, Karl Lott, 1953 (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Rao, Paul P., 1955 (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Rashid, Baddia J., 1955-1956 (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Rayburn, Sam, 1949 (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Read, Dr. David H. C., 1956-1967 (Box 134, Folder 5)
      Includes the text of the sermons "This Year of Grace," "Faith and the New Fatalism," and "Why the Reformation Lives and Grows" preached in the Madison Avenue Presbyterian Church in New York.
    - Redmond, Roland L., 1939 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Reece, Carroll, 1948 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Reed, Guy E., 1948-1953 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Reed, Philip D., 1948 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Reid, Ogden, 1944-1964 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Reid, Whitelaw, 1948-1952 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Reinert, Reverend Paul C., 1955 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Reiser, Professor Oliver, 1964-1966 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Reisner, Reverend Christian F., 1936-1940 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Relin, Bernard, 1952-1966 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Repplier, Theodore, 1955 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Resor, Stanley, 1938-1962 (Box 135, Folder 1)
      Includes press releases from the United Church Canvass.
    - Reynolds, Quentin, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Rhee, Syngman, 1944-1955 (Box 135, Folder 1)
      Includes correspondence from Louise Yim, a press release from The Korean Commission, and an untitled essay by Rhee "regarding the sentiment of the Asiatic people after the Japanese war." Correspondence from Rhee consists of copies.
    - Rhyne, Charles S., 1959-1960 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Ribeiro, Victor, 1967 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Richards, Guy, 1945 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Richards, Ira, 1936-1939 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Richards, John, 1939 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Rickenbacker, Edward V., 1946-1951 (Box 135, Folder 1)
      Includes a sticker from Eastern Air Lines.
    - Rickover, Admiral H. G., 1960-1961 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Rieber, T., 1936-1940 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Riemer, George, 1964-1965 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Ritter, Roger E., 1937-1960 (Box 135, Folder 2)
      Includes a spiral bound notebook with copies of letters of reference, a resume with an attached photograph of Ritter, and photographs of showrooms with glass and porcelain. In addition there is a photograph of Mr. and Mrs. Ritter and the exterior view of the house they are living in.
    - Rizzoli, Angelo, 1955 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Roberts, Roy, 1952 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Robinson, Professor Edgar E., 1950-1962 (Box 135, Folder 2)
      Includes Robinson's speech "History in the Making."
    - Rockefeller, David, 1942-1959 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Jr. John D., 1943-1948 (Box 135, Folder 2)
      Correspondence from Rockefeller consists of copies.
    - Rockefeller, III John D., 1941-1961 (Box 135, Folder 3)
      Includes a brochure from the American Youth Hostels, Inc., and the pamphlet "Colonial Williamsburg: The First Twenty-Five Years: A Report by the President as of December 31, 1951." Correspondents from Rockefeller consists of copies.
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1939-1966 (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop, 1939-1948 (Box 135, Folder 3)
      Includes preliminary findings of the survey "Youth and Aviation in the United States."
    - Rodell, Fred, 1951 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Rogers, Mrs. Cobb, 1947-1954 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Rogers, William P., 1961 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Rolandi, Gian, 1953 (Box 135, Folder 4)
      Includes the report "Mrs. Luce's Visit to Milan" regarding her appointment as ambassador to Italy.
    - Roli, Mario, 1953-1956 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Romney, George, 1962 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Romulo, Carlos P., 1949-1965 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1939-1945 (Box 135, Folder 4)
      Includes a White House admittance card, and copies of letters from Franklin and Eleanor Roosevelt.
    - Roosevelt, Mrs. Kermit, 1939-1947 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Roosevelt, Jr. Colonel Theodore, 1935-1948 (Box 135, Folder 4)
      Correspondence from Roosevelt consists of copies.
    - Root, Jr. Oren, 1942-1961 (Box 135, Folder 4)
      Includes memoranda on the Committee on Fair Employment Practice (FEPC).
    - Rootes, Sir William, 1944 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Roots, John McCook, 1936-1965 (Box 135, Folder 5)
      Includes the hardcover book Warrior's Testament with an inscription to HRL on the inside leaf, a photograph of Dr. Chen Li-Fu receiving a cake from the farmer's wife at the premier of the play "The Good Road" in Caux, Switzerland, a program for the World Assembly Industrial Conference, the report "Appraisal of the Moral Re-Armament Movement," the pamphlet "Mission to the West" published by Moral Re-Armament, and the memo "U.S. Policy in China."
    - Roots, Logan, 1938-1945 (Box 136, Folder 1)
      Includes the pamphlet "Moral Rearmament Through Sport," and photographs of Root and his funeral procession with a village in the background.
    - Roper, Elmo, 1943-1967 (Box 136, Folder 1)
      Includes a printed copy of a "Plan for a Conference on the State of the Union" by S. Stanwood Menken.
    - Rorimer, James, 1966 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Rosenberg, James N., 1958-1959 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Rosenbluth, Milton, 1942-1958 (Box 136, Folder 1)
      Includes a summary of a medical examination of HRL, and a pamphlet with Rosenbluth's article "The Practical Management of Hypertension."
    - Rosengrant, John, 1953 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Rosenstiel, Lewis S., 1953-1965 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Rosenwald, Lessing J., 1947 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Rosini, Giuseppe, 1954 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Ross, Emory, 1939-1942 (Box 136, Folder 2)
      Includes a program and seating list of the Christian Foreign Service Convocation Luncheon held under the auspices of The Foreign Mission Conference of North America, and a signed carbon copy of a letter from W. Harry Coxill regarding sending his nieces from England to the United States due to World War II.
    - Rossi-Longhi, Alberto, 1955 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Rostow, Walter W., 1958 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Rothermere, Lord, 1939-1946 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Roxas, Manuel, 1946 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Rubel, Roy L., 1955 (Box 136, Folder 2)
      Includes a bound set of clippings on Clare Boothe Luce in Italy.
    - Rubicam, Raymond, 1943-1960 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Rubloff, Arthur, 1955 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Rueff, Jacques, 1960-1964 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Rule, Victor A., 1947-1957 (Box 136, Folder 2)
      Includes a brochure from The University Club of New York, and an original signed letter from Nelson A. Rockefeller.
    - Ruml, Beardsley, 1947-1955 (Box 136, Folder 3)
      Includes Ruml's speeches "Taxes, the Budget and the Debt" and "The Interest Rate Problem."
    - Rusk, Dean, 1962 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Rusk, Howard, 1954 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Russell, Frank F., 1940 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Russell, John, 1953-1954 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Saarinen, Eero, 1961 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Sachs, Alexander, 1938-1939 (Box 136, Folder 3)
      Includes extracts from "Memorandum Letter on Independence of Administrative Boards and Government Reorganization."
    - Sadler, George B., 1943 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Saltonstall, Leverett, 1944 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Saltzman, C. E., 1954 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Salzano, Carlo, 1958 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Samish, Arthur H., 1943 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Sampson, William, 1933-1954 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Sandburg, Carl, 1939-1940 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Sanger, Margaret, 1942 (Box 136, Folder 3)
      Includes an original signed letter and an invitation to attend a Planned Parenthood conference.
    - Saragat, Giuseppe, 1955 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Sargeant, J. Weir, 1939-1965 (Box 136, Folder 3)
      Includes a photograph of an artificial Christmas tree.
    - Sarnoff, David, 1940-1965 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Sauer, Carl A., 1962-1965 (Box 136, Folder 4)
      Includes brochures with a proposal to help those in retirement to generate social, economic and humanitarian benefits.
    - Saulnier, Raymond J., 1963 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Sayre, Sr. and Jr. Francis B., 1941-1959 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Scaife, Alan M. (Mr. and Mrs.), 1933-1960 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Scandone, F., 1955 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Scarlatta, Giuseppe, 1953 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Scelba, Mario, 1955 (Box 136, Folder 4)
      Includes tickets to a special convocation at Columbia University, a draft of Clare Boothe Luce's schedule on her trip to the United States from Italy, and an official invitation to HRL from President and Mrs. Eisenhower.
    - Scerni, Mario, 1955 (Box 136, Folder 4)
      Includes financial information on the Italo-American Association.
    - Schaffer, Fritz, 1953 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Scheer, Anton and Alice, 1946-1953 (Box 136, Folder 5)
      Includes a photographic postcard with the image of the ship USS Lejeune, and correspondence sent from China. Also includes eight small photographs with most containing two small girls at Peking and other sites in China. A later photograph has Scheer with two of the girls as teenagers.
    - Schermerhorn, A. C., 1933-1956 (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Schiff, John M., 1939 (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Schlamm, Willi, 1947-1963 (Box 136, Folder 5)
      Includes a letter with attachments announcing the launch of the National Review magazine and a translation from German of the Schlamm column "Down to Facts" on Father Time.
    - Schlesinger, Jr. Arthur, 1965 (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Schlesinger, Rudolph B., 1959-1961 (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Schlieker, Willy H., 1957-1961 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Schmidt, Elisabeth, 1954 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Schmidt, Walter S., 1951 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Schuster, M. Lincoln, 1962-1963 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Schneider, Ernst, 1954 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Schwartz, Mrs. Morton L., 1937 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Schwarz, Millie, 1951 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Scott, Albert L., 1937 (Box 137, Folder 1)
      Includes an issue of A Bulletin of Research and Review issued by A Movement for World Christianity.
    - Scott, Charles E., 1941-1942 (Box 137, Folder 1)
      Includes a form letter from Warren A. Seavey asking for the support of China in their fight against Japan.
    - Scott, Hugh, 1959 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Scranton, William, 1965 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Scranton, Mrs. Worthington, 1955-1956 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Searle, Reverend Robert W., 1937-1950 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Seaton, Fred A., 1960-1961 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Seay, Harry L., 1940 (Box 137, Folder 1)
      Includes photographs of dead ducks, geese, and deer following a hunt. Two of the photos have men holding up the dead birds.
    - Seldes, Gilbert, 1933 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Segni, Antonio, 1955-1964 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Selfridge, Sr. and Jr. Gordon, 1937-1939 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Seligman, Eustace, 1935-1961 (Box 137, Folder 2)
      Includes a brochure from The Foreign Policy Association, the brochure "Abolish the Slums" from the National Public Housing Conference, and a speech of Fiorello La Guardia at the Men's Round Table Luncheon Discussion.
    - Seltzer, Louis B., 1941-1965 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Selznick, Irene Mayer, 1957-1965 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Selznick, David O., 1933-1965 (Box 137, Folder 3)
      Includes correspondence dealing with United China Relief, the visit of Madame Chiang Kai-shek to the United States, and a draft of the poem "Help China or Out of Suffering" by Edgar A. Guest.
    - Sewall, Sumner, 1943 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Seymour, Charles, 1937-1950 (Box 137, Folder 4)
      Includes the booklet "Report of the President of Yale University to the Alumni 1940-1941" and a pamphlet with Seymour's speech "Dedicated to Service of Nation."
    - Sgueglia, Yolande, 1955 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Shannon, Reverend James P., 1965-1966 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Shapley, Harlow, 1946 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Sharman, Abbie Lyon, 1932-1933 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Sheed, Frank, 1951 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Sheen, Bishop Fulton J., 1949-1958 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Sheil, Bishop Bernard J., 1945 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Shelden, Alger, 1933-1964 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Sheldon, Sherwood, 1944 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Shepardson, Whitney H., 1940-1959 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Shepherd, Lemuel C., 1950 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Sherwood, Carlton M., 1941 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Sherwood, Robert, 1940-1951 (Box 137, Folder 4)
      Includes a letter discussing the formation of a National Propaganda Bureau.
    - Shipler, Guy Emory, 1941 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Shreve, Reverend Charles, 1954 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Shivers, Allan, 1949 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Shuster, George N., 1950-1951 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Sidenberg, Jr. George M., 1940-1954 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Sidlo, Thomas L., 1942 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Sillani, Tomaso, 1954-1956 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Simpson, Dean C. A., 1959-1967 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Simpson, Kenneth, 1939-1943 (Box 137, Folder 5)
      Includes untitled speeches made by Simpson, and a carbon copy of an analysis titled "1940 Presidential Election Comments."
    - Singh, Sirdar J. J., 1948-1958 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Sinsabaugh, R. W., 1942 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Sioussat, Helen J., 1953-1961 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Skouras, Spyros P., 1945-1961 (Box 138, Folder 1)
      Includes a thermofax copy of a letter from Skouras to President Eisenhower regarding the problem of Cyprus.
    - Sloan, Jr. Alfred P., 1958 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Sloan, George A., 1939-1940 (Box 138, Folder 1)
      Includes Sloan's speech "What's Ahead for American Industry?"
    - Sloanaker, Hiram L., 1948-1963 (Box 138, Folder 1)
      Includes the poem "Up and Down" by Sloanaker.
    - Smadbeck, Arthur, 1959 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Smith, Alfred E., 1942-1956 (Box 138, Folder 1)
      Does not contain correspondence from Smith.
    - Smith, Charles D., 1933-1955 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Smith, Edward H., 1944 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Smith, Harrison, 1947 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Smith, Henry Justin, 1961 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Kenneth J., 1953 (Box 138, Folder 2)
      Includes a letter from Eugene E. Barnett.
    - Smith, Paul, 1941-1959 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Robert L., 1942-1950 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Smith, William T., 1943 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Truman, 1944 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Walter Bedell, 1950-1954 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Snell, Frank, 1965-1967 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Snow, Edgar P., 1941-1944 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Sockman, Dr. Ralph W., 1945-1966 (Box 138, Folder 2)
      Includes a brochure for the World's Sunday School Association.
    - Sogno, Count Edgardo, 1955 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Soong, Dr. T. V., 1933-1965 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Sorine, Savely, 1937 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Spalding, H. N., 1941 (Box 138, Folder 3)
      Includes a carbon copy of the Constitution of the East and West Cultural Association.
    - Spater, R. P., 1956 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Speer, Robert, 1938-1952 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Speers, William E., 1947 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Spellman, Cardinal Francis, 1941-1966 (Box 138, Folder 3)
      Includes invitations to The Alfred E. Smith Memorial Dinner, Spellman's speech "America Look Homeward!" and an untitled address delivered in front of the Society of the Friendly Sons of St. Patrick. Correspondence from Spellman consists of copies.
    - Spender, Sir Percy, 1958 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Springer, Axel, 1953-1954 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Spruance, Raymond, 1953 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Spykman, Nicholas J., 1943 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Stafford, Russell Henry, 1950 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Standley, William Harrison, 1940 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Stanford, Henry King, 1963-1966 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Stanley, Oliver, 1939? (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Starr, Cornelius V., 1937-1946 (Box 138, Folder 4)
      Includes an issue of the newspaper Ambassador.
    - Starr, Jr. Edward, 1933 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Stassen, Harold, 1942-1950 (Box 138, Folder 4)
      Includes a brochure for the Crusade for Freedom.
    - Steichen, Edward, 1937-1945 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Steinert, Eleanor H., 1959-1967 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Steinhardt, Lawrence, 1940-1950 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Sterling, J. E. Wallace, 1955 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Stettinius, Edward, 1944 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Stevens, Bertram, 1951 (Box 138, Folder 4)
      Includes a broadcast address made by Stevens on Station 2FC (Guest-of-Honor Series) the Australian National Network.
    - Stevens, Robert T., 1953 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Stevens, Roger L., 1965-1966 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Stevens, Samuel N., 1954 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Stevenson, Adlai E., 1963 (Box 138, Folder 5)
      Contains copy of an invitation to serve as a member of the Council for the Eleanor Roosevelt Memorial.
    - Stevenson, Edward Ford, 1935-1939 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Stewart, George, 1937-1956 (Box 138, Folder 5)
      Includes a printed appeal titled "Have We Not Seen and Heard Enough to Make Up Our Minds?" from the Fight For Freedom Committee, and a report on the lecture tour of Dr. Stewart in the Middle East.
    - Stewart, Jr. W. J., 1946 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Stewart, Mrs. William Rhinelander, 1945 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Stichova, Eva, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 5)
      Includes a biography of the artist Svatopluk Sulek and seven photographs of his paintings.
    - Stifler, Francis, 1936 (Box 138, Folder 5)
      Contains correspondence between Stifler and Henry Winter Luce.
    - Stillwell, Joseph W., 1942 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Stimson, Henry, 1947-1948 (Box 139, Folder 1)
      Includes copies of correspondence regarding Chiang Kai-shek.
    - Stimson, Jonathan Cass, 1940 (Box 139, Folder 1)
      Includes a telegram regarding Wendell Willkie.
    - Stone, Edward Durrell, 1936-1978 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Stone, John T., 1953 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Stookey, Byron, 1937 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Stout, William B., 1939 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Stratton, Elbridge, 1933 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Stratton, Samuel S., 1966 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Strauss, Lewis L., 1958-1959 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Strausz-Hupe, Robert, 1959-1961 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Streit, Clarence, 1941-1960 (Box 139, Folder 2)
      Includes a page proof of an advertisement "Defense Now Needs Union Now: A Proposal that the USA and the Six British Democracies form a Federal Union Before it is too Late," the pamphlet "Federal Union of the Free," printed draft titled "Declaration and Joint Resolution of the Congress of the United States," printed notes of a conversation between Streit and General Eisenhower, the speech "We Can Win Without World War," issues of the magazine Freedom & Union, outline and first chapter of the manuscript for the book Freedom Against Itself, and a large amount of correspondence and memoranda regarding the Federal Union movement.
    - Stroup, Russell C., 1948-1965 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Stuart, Sir Campbell, 1942 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Stuart, Dr. J. Leighton, 1933-1956 (Box 139, Folder 3)
      Includes the pamphlet "Concerning Yenching University's Department of Journalism in 1936," form letters to the Board of Trustees of Yenching University, and minutes of the meeting of the Steering Committee of the Promotion Committee of the Associated Boards for Christian Colleges in China.
    - Stueber, Ralph, 1933 (Box 139, Folder 3)
      Includes a brochure advertising Joe Mitchell Chapple's speaking engagements, and a proposal for a magazine devoted to announcements of authentic prize contests and winners.
    - Sturm, Justin (Mr. and Mrs.), 1958-1963 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Sudler, Carroll H., 1957 (Box 139, Folder 3)
      Includes the brief memoir My Mother by "Son Cully."
    - Suenens, Cardinal Leon J., 1964 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Sullivan, Mark, 1936-1938 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Sulzberger, Arthur Hays, 1937-1957 (Box 139, Folder 4)
      Includes a pamphlet with the address made by Sulzberger to the graduating class of John Carroll University.
    - Summerfield, Arthur E., 1959 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Sun, Li-Jen, 1954 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Sun, T. H., 1935 (Box 139, Folder 4)
      Includes an English and a Chinese version of the magazine The Christian Farmer.
    - Swaine, Robert T., 1941-1945 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Swift, Harold H., 1937 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Swift, Kay, 1935 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Swope, Herbert Bayard, 1935-1957 (Box 139, Folder 5)
      Includes Swope's address "Free Speech" delivered at the Veterans of Foreign Wars National Encampment, and a photograph of the Bernard M. Baruch bus and emplacement located at Baruch Houses. Correspondence from Swope consists of copies.
    - Symington, Stuart, 1959 (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - Taft, Charles P., 1933-1962 (Box 139, Folder 5)
      Includes remarks made by Taft at Riverside Church, NY, and a booklet from The Emergency Peace Campaign labeled "No-Foreign-War Crusade: A Handbook of Ways and Means by Which Individuals and Groups May Help to Keep the United States Out of War and Promote World Peace" on the inside cover, the publication The Bugle published by Christian Soldiers, Inc., and a news bulletin from the Charles P. Taft for Governor Committee.
    - Taft, Robert, 1937-1947 (Box 140, Folder 1)
      Correspondence from Taft consists of copies.
    - Talbott, Jr. Harold E., 1935-1952 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Tarchiani, Alberto, 1953-1955 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Taylor, Arthur, 1946-1950 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Taylor, Francis Henry, 1953-1957 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Taylor, Henry C., 1941 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Taylor, Henry J., 1942-1966 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Taylor, Maxwell, 1956-1957 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Taylor, Reese H., 1939 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Taylor, Vernon F., 1935-1953 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Taylor, W. R. K., 1933 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Terry, Hugh B., 1966 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Temianka, Henri, 1966 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Thacker, Earl M., 1937-1959 (Box 140, Folder 2)
      Includes the pamphlet "Report of the President Before the 57th Annual Meeting of the Hawaiian Sugar Planters' Association."
    - Thayer, J. A., 1955-1956 (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Thomas, Horace, 1958 (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Thomas, Lowell, 1938-1950 (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Thomas, Norman, [1940?]-1953 (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Thompson, Dorothy, 1937-1954 (Box 140, Folder 3)
      Includes a statement concerning the need for re-declaration of American faith titled "Declaration of Independence - 1939," pamphlets with Thompson's radio speeches, and correspondence and memoranda regarding the creation of the American Friends of the Middle East.
    - Thornburg, Leila and Max (folder 1 of 2), 1941-1964 (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Thornburg, Leila and Max (folder 2 of 2) - oversize, circa 1933 (Box OS-Large)
      Contains a large map of Iran in French labeled "Carte Physique, Politique et Economique" made by E. Girard.
    - Thorne, Jr. Landon K., 1953-1964 (Box 140, Folder 4)
      Includes a list of major United States investments in Italy, and the memorandum "Private Investment."
    - Thorneycroft, Rt. Hon. Peter, 1957-1961 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Thornton, R. L., 1944-1964 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Thrasher, Corinne, 1942-1951 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Thurston, Lorrin P., 1937-1938 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Thye, Edward, 1943 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Tiarks, Henry F., 1949-1954 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Tillich, Dr. Paul A., 1963-1966 (Box 140, Folder 4)